the majority it's... everyone is just very black clothes
so i felt like Amy kind of stood out because she was wearing a white dress
and like other clothes that didn't quite fit
but that's not a problem
and there weren't that many blonde girls you know in the crowd
but there are still quite a few
but It felt like, oh, I'm back in Korea,
you know, being kind of standing out in the group.
So, yeah, so we got in
and then I had seen on Instagram that the day before Friday was the first concert in Oakland,
that there were very short lines for different merch sections selling just the light sticks in certain spots of the stadium.
And at that time, the lines were very short
people didn't know about them
i guess there were other sections for other merch
and then there were the merch stores outside open to the public
so we went to go try to get there
we're like okay we got there right when the doors opened
we weren't that late
hopefully we can get in line
and i wanted to buy one of the light sticks
but i don't know if
just the person who made the film the video
If they went at like a very odd time,
maybe they were first in line
or everyone had seen the same video I did and knew to go,
but the line was very long.
And so we gave up.
We got food, some popcorn and water.
It was very expensive.
I didn't realize how expensive it was gonna be for one bottle of water.
I think it was $8.
We were the very top.
Like I think there was maybe four or
five rows. behind us
the nosebleed seats yeah
we were definitely in the nosebleed seats
it's the third tier of the coliseum
it's an open air stadium
um the concert was starting at eight
so definitely by the time the sun was going down
it was like oh man
it's it's getting cold um
luckily once the concert started though
with all the people packed in
and everyone screaming
and you know dancing in your seats and stuff
you didn't notice
Throughout the entire concert, it was really funny.
They were just very silly, joking, laughing.
It did not feel like a super serious, scripted setup.
So obviously Taeyang,
he knows everyone wants to see him with his shirt off.
But he kept saying, "
No, it's too cold, it's too cold.
You need to make it hotter in here."
It was up to us to make it hot so he didn't catch a cold.
So he just kind of really played that up to see whether or not he was going to take his shirt off
during his solo set.
Daesung definitely made jokes about his appearance. especially features of his face
Taeyang went and grabbed Daesung's belt buckle
and i both me and Amy thought we heard him say this girl
so we were wondering if he had like a girl's name written on the belt buckle
but it turns out it was a brand name that said d squared
so he kept saying d squared d squared
and Daesung was covering it just to show the ds which i realized after like oh that's the initials of his name.
Maybe that's why he was wearing it,
but it was just like a very weird but silly thing that happened.
It was really enjoyable.
It kind of at the very end made it seem...
Because like we were sure is this the end of the concert? Is it done? Is it not?
Like they just kept going.
So it was a little unorganized at the end.
But it made it really silly.
Maybe in English, the way they were saying it came across more silly
or like they were making mistakes and it turned into something humorous.
I don't really know,
but it was entertaining and Amy really liked it.
Oakland is just such a weird spot.
But what we Amy said she did here,
a lot of people flew in for the concert
so i guess that makes sense that they picked Oakland
because the Oakland international airport is the same Bart station
so it is just right there
like people who flew in could literally just stay at those hotels and be very close
so i don't know if that's part of the reason why they picked Oakland
or i think BTS had a concert in LA the same weekend
and then just with all of football season starting.
I don't know if a lot of stadiums were full,
but it just felt Oakland felt random to me.
Maybe there's some thing I don't know,
but it felt random.